https://www.ricelake.com/en-us/support/privacy-policy

×
Choose the location nearest you:
English (United States)Español (México)Türkçe (Türkiye)Nederlands (Nederland)Français (France)English (United Kingdom)Deutsch (Deutschland)Español (España, Alfabetización Internacional)
Dini Argeo (diniargeo.com)
Rice Lake India
Português (Brasil)
Español (Argentina)
privacy policy, Rice Lake Weighing Systems, Inc. may be referred to as
“Rice Lake,” “we,” “us” or “our,” or terms of similar import, while the
website user may be referred to as “user,” “you” and “your,” or terms of
similar import.
We
respect and are committed to protecting your privacy. That is why we have
adopted this privacy policy, which lets you know how your personal information
is processed and used. We will take steps to use your personal information only
in ways that are compatible with this privacy policy. The following policies
are only in effect for the web pages, newsletters and opt-in announcement lists
owned by Rice Lake. The Rice Lake network consists of the
Rice Lake website and other websites and Internet media properties hyperlinked
from the Rice Lake website, including corporate social media platforms.
Please
review this privacy policy. If you have any problems with authorizing
Rice Lake to collect, store, use and handle information in the manner
described in this privacy policy, you should stop using Rice Lake websites
and its Internet properties.
What Information Is Rice Lake Collecting and How Is Rice Lake Collecting It?
Every
computer that is connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of
numbers that serve as the computer's Internet Protocol address (IP address).
When a visitor requests a page from any website within the Rice Lake
network, our web servers automatically recognize that visitor's domain name and
IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about you
other than the IP address from which you have accessed our site. We use this
information to examine our traffic in the aggregate, and to investigate misuse
of the Rice Lake network, its users or to cooperate with law enforcement.
(See also the section in this privacy policy titled “Will Rice Lake
Disclose the Information It Collects to Outside Third Parties?”)
What Are Cookies?
From
time to time, Rice Lake may send a "cookie" to your computer. A
cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your Internet browser from a web
server and stored on your computer's hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off
your computer’s hard disk or read cookie files created by other websites.
Cookies do not damage your system. We use cookies to identify which areas of
Rice Lake's network you have visited, so the next time you visit, those
pages may be readily accessible.
We may
also use cookies to help serve you online advertising messages based on
previously visited web pages on our websites and Internet properties through
remarketing. We may ascertain how many times you've seen a Rice Lake web page
or advertisement. We use this information to better personalize content,
banners and promotions that you see on our website. We also use this
information to advertise to you through third-party vendors, including Google®.
This allows us to show you Rice Lake advertisements on sites and mediums across
the Internet. These third-party vendors use cookies to serve you remarketed ads
based on your Rice Lake website visits.
You can choose whether to accept these cookies
by changing the settings of your Internet browser. You can reset your browser
to refuse all cookies, or allow your browser to show you when a cookie is being
sent. If you choose not to accept these cookies, your experience on our site
and other websites may be diminished and some features may not work as
intended. You can also opt out of Google’s use of cookies for remarketing
purposes by visiting
Google’s Ad Settings.
What Information Does Rice Lake Collect When I Register?
Rice Lake
offers access to some services that require registration. We may use your
registration contact information to send you notifications of Rice Lake
products and services by email and/or postal mail. We may also share that
information with our distributors/dealers. Our distributors/dealers might send
you promotional material related to the topic of the service for which you
registered. We may also use your IP address internally.
Your
email or mailing address could be requested for the purpose of conducting a
survey to provide additional services. Whenever we request the identity of the
visitor, we will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the
information is requested. We maintain a strict "No-Spam" policy. That
means we do not sell, rent or otherwise give your email address to any
third-party without your consent or as permitted by this policy.
When
you register for a contest or other promotion, we may ask for your name,
address and email address so we can administer the contest and notify winners.
We may also use this information to ensure you have agreed to any applicable
contest rules.
What Information Does Rice Lake Collect When I Purchase Something?
If you
are purchasing something from a Rice Lake media property, we need to know
your name, address, email address, credit card number and expiration date. This
allows us to process and fulfill your order, and to notify you of your order
status. Your credit card and other information will not be shared or sold to
any third parties.
Certain
Rice Lake properties use a shopping cart feature that safeguards this
information by using industry standard SSL (Secure Socket Layer) encrypted
servers. SSL codes the information transferred between you and the server,
rendering it unreadable to anyone trying to interpret the information. Other
Rice Lake properties do not use the SSL; therefore, they do not offer a
secure coded way to transfer information.
Will Rice Lake Disclose the Information It Collects to Outside Third Parties?
Any
personal or individual information you provide to Rice Lake is held or
shared only by Rice Lake, its associated companies or its representatives
and agents who are acting on our behalf with regard to your activity.
We do
not rent, sell or exchange mailing lists or responses of individual visitors to
or with any other unaffiliated third parties. We respect the information you
provide to us and treat it carefully. Rice Lake will disclose personal
information and/or your IP address when required by law or in the good faith
belief that such action is necessary.
Rice Lake
uses reasonable precautions to keep secure any information disclosed to us.
Rice Lake reserves the right to transfer all such information in
connection with the sale of all or part of Rice Lake capital stock or
assets. Furthermore, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for
any actions of any third parties that receive the information. We are not
responsible for such third party privacy policies or how they treat information
about their users.
Your Acknowledgment of this Privacy Policy
By
using the Rice Lake network, you consent to the collection and use of
information by Rice Lake as specified in this privacy policy. If we decide
to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so you're
always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what
circumstances we disclose it. You should check back periodically with this
privacy policy to see if, and how, it may change over time. Again, if you have
any objections to Rice Lake collecting and handling information in the
manner described in this privacy policy, you should not use or stop using
Rice Lake websites.
If you
have any questions about this policy, please contact Rice Lake at
webteam@ricelake.com, or see our contact us section for information on contacting Rice Lake via
mail.
© Rice Lake Weighing Systems. All rights reserved.
